Okay. So, today we're going to be
installing Visual Studio Code on a
Windows. So, what I want you to do is I
want you to come to your Google search
and type in download Visual Studio Code.
And then you're going to click the first
website.
And then here you can see we've got
Windows and we've got Mac. We are on a
Windows, so we're going to install with
Windows. It's going to take a second to
download. It's going to download an
executable file. Once that's done, go
ahead and open up that file.
It's going to take a second to load. Um,
we want to read through this agreement.
I've downloaded this before, so I'm
going to accept this agreement and hit
next. Um, I do want a desktop icon, so
I'm going to check the Slack box. And
then I'm going to hit next. And then
it's hit install. And then it's going to
take some time to install.
So we'll run for a little bit. And I'm
going to actually pause and cut until
the install is done. Really, it only
takes a few minutes.
So I really only cut out about 44
seconds there. And we are done. And so
we'll hit finish and launch. And that
should launch our Visual Studio Code.
takes a second to load, but if you see a
screen somewhat like this, then it means
you've correctly installed Visual Studio
Code and you are safe to move on to the
next video.